Guide to the Francis B. (Francis Butler) Loomis Papers: microfilm, 1897-1939
Department of Special Collections
- Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and His Antecedents in the Old World, Series 8; 1 microfilm reel
As located in the National Union Catalogue of Manuscript Collections and the List of Record Groups of the National Archives and Records Service
Library of Congress
MS 66-1455 William I., Scruggs Papers
West Virginia University Library
MS 66-754 Woodbridge Mercantile Co. Records
Materials Related to Loomis and the Panama Canal
Georgetown University Archives
MS 67-94 Toms Herran Papers
Library of Congress
MS 60-1722 John Bigelow Papers
MS 62-4655 Philippe Bunau-Varilla Papers
MS 64-767 Andrew Carnegie Papers
MS 71-1353 Roscoe F. Dillen Papers
MS 59-28 Philander C. Knox Papers
New York Historical Society
MS 60-2699 Julio Betancourt Papers
State Historical Society of Wisconsin
MS 62-2352 William G. Haan Papers
University of Michigan Transportation Library
MS 62-2675 Francis L. Stuart Papers
Western Reserve Historical Society, Cleveland
MS 62-4384 Theodore E. Burton Papers
National Archives
76 NNFD Boundary and Claims Commissions and Arbitrations
285 NC Commerce, Department of International Commercial Operations.
84 NNFD Foreign Service Posts of the Department of State
43 NNFD International Conferences, Commissions, and Expositions
59 NNFD State, Department of. Special List #7 List of Documents Relating to Special Agents of Departments 1789-1906
Further information on Loomis' career can be found in Theodore Roosevelt's Papers, John Hay's Papers, and various collections which deal with particular foreign policy questions for the period between 1890-1912.